latestjobs.co.in 2019-06-21

# Privacy Policy - Latest Govt Jobs

### **Privacy Policy for https://latestjobs.co.in**

**Log Files**

https://latestjobs.co.in follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

**Google DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.website.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>

**Our Advertising Partners**

Some of advertisers on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.

  * Google

<https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>

**Privacy Policies**

You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of https://latestjobs.co.in.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on https://latestjobs.co.in, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that https://latestjobs.co.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Third Pary Privacy Policies**

https://latestjobs.co.in’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?

**What information do we collect?**

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your Name, Email address or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

**How do we protect visitor information?**

  * We only provide articles and information, and we never ask for personal or private information

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

**We use cookies to:**

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart,
  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits,
  * Keep track of advertisements,

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

It will turn off some of the features of the site

_Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on https://latestjobs.co.in._

_Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to  https://latestjobs.co.in ’s users based on their visit to https://latestjobs.co.in and other sites on the Internet._

_Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network[privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Users from European Union countries may check here at  [Cookies notification in European Union countries](https://support.google.com/blogger/answer/6253244?p=eu_cookies_notice&hl=en&rd=1)_

**Note:**  Your IP address or demographic information in never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

Children’s Information

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

https://latestjobs.co.in does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

Online Privacy Policy Only

[This privacy policy (created with the GDPR Generator)](https://gdprprivacynotice.com/) applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in https://latestjobs.co.in. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, latestjobs.co.in may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in latestjobs.co.in ’s sole discretion. latestjobs.co.in encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Contact Us  **

If You Have any queary about latestjobs.co.in (any Post wise Information) then Please Contact us on through this E-mail : **joydeep.jobs@yahoocom**. Our Site Administrator will be listining your Valueable query and answering them.

latestjobs.co.in will not be liable for any cost or damage arising either directly or indirectly from any condition.

All rights are reserved by latestjobs.co.in © 2018 | ( **Legal Copyright Diary No. 3653/2018-CO/SW** )

Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.

Latest Govt Jobs © 2018-19 - latestjobs.co.in © 2018-19 | Legal Copyright Diary No. 3653/2018-CO/SW ........Important Note : please visit the official website for detailed information, the above information in this page may not be complete.
